cenhud.com 2015-11-10

# Central Hudson Gas & Electric - Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting the Central Hudson Web site and reviewing our privacy policy. Central Hudson is committed to your privacy and security.

Central Hudson has created this privacy statement to help you understand how we collect and use information when you visit www.CentralHudson.com:

Personally identifiable information that you voluntarily submit ("customer information") is used solely for Central Hudson’s purposes. We do not sell or otherwise share customer lists, and will not disclose your customer information to third parties that may want to market products or services to you. We may, however, need to share specific information with third-party business partners or contractors when that information is required in order to answer your inquiry, to fulfill your request for a product or service, or to otherwise conduct our business with you, including the collection of payment from you.

In addition, though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law or to comply with a judicial proceeding, a subpoena, a court order, or other legal process.

Central Hudson has implemented policy guidelines and security features to access specific customer-account information and to help safeguard customer-specific account information from unauthorized access or improper use.

Central Hudson uses software to automatically collect non-personal information about your visit for statistical purposes. This information, such as the name of the domain from which you access the Internet, the date and time you access our Web site, and the information you view while visiting our Web site, is used to measure the use of our site, to improve its content, and to diagnose and correct technical problems.

Central Hudson gathers and uses customer information in order to inform you of products and services, for billing purposes, and to resolve problems. Correspondence that you send, including e-mail, or forms you fill out to request products, services, or information, may require personal information such as your account number, home or business address, e-mail address, telephone number, or other specific information. We use this information to respond to your requests and to transact business with you.

Some of our Web site pages may use "cookies" – small amounts of data that a Web site can send to you and that is stored on your computer. Cookies allow our Web site to provide you with customized information, or they may recall data so you don't have to retype it. We may use session ID cookies, which terminate when you close your Internet browser, or persistent cookies, a small text file stored on your computer's hard drive for an extended time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions.

Periodically, we administer online surveys to gather information about your use of energy and related products and services, or to obtain your views on the usefulness of our Web site. Participation in our online surveys is voluntary. If you choose to participate, the information you provide will be used to improve our site and the products and services we offer to you.

Links to Other Sites: Please note that our Web site contains links to other sites. We provide links that we think will be of interest or benefit to our customers and others who visit our Web site. While we strive to provide links to sites that share our respect for our customers, we are not responsible for their content or their privacy practices.

Children's Privacy: While we maintain energy-related educational content directed at children under the age of 13, our site does not collect or maintain personal information from children under the age of 13.

Corrections to Your Customer Information: If you believe any of your customer information that we collect or maintain is incorrect, please write to us at: 284 South Ave. Poughkeepsie, NY 12601.

Modifications to this Policy: Central Hudson may modify this policy from time to time to reflect legal, technological, or other developments. Any modifications will appear on the Privacy Policy page at www.CentralHudson.com.  
Compliance: If you have questions about this privacy policy, or if you believe that we are not following the policy as it is set forth here, you may contact us by writing to us at our mailing address: 284 South Ave, Poughkeepsie, NY 12601.
